<trivia>
	

<item category="Lore">

<question>The Trinity expansion had a tendency to erase what Windows critical system file?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>boot.ini</answer>
			
<answer>audiosrv.dll</answer>
			
<answer>dll32.exe</answer>
			
<answer>config.sys</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>What's the shape of Italy?</hint>
		
<fact>The initial version of the Trinity patch could under certain circumstances delete the player's operating system's boot.ini file, thus rendering the operating system unbootable.</fact>
	
</item>
	
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>If a Russian in EVE follows a sentence with the word 'cyka', what do they mean? </question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>It's likely that you just got called a bitch. </answer>
			
<answer>Russian word for Friend, used after smooth trades.</answer>
			
<answer>Cynosural Field is ready.</answer>
			
<answer>A signal in local chat telling their fleet to warp in and Gank you.</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>Hostile</hint>
		
<fact>*Salutes Roman* ; _ ; Russian word for bitch. "Doing judo moves and schooling, every communist cyka"</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>What is the Walking in Stations Expansion called?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Incarna</answer>
			
<answer>Oceanus</answer>
			
<answer>Apocrypha</answer>
			
<answer>Exodus</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>It's not Apocrypha</hint>
		
<fact>Previously known as 'Ambulation' and 'Walking In Stations', the overall Incarna feature revolves around allowing players to leave their pods and walk around in their station HQ.</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>The Trinity Expansion gave the game an updated graphics engine. What year was it released?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>2007</answer>
			
<answer>2006</answer>
			
<answer>2008</answer>
			
<answer>2009</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>Before 2009</hint>
		
<fact>Release date: December 5, 2007</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Gallenteans are mainly colonizers from what modern day country?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>France</answer>
			
<answer>United States</answer>
			
<answer>Spain</answer>
			
<answer>Germany</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>PTW has a way cooler bunch from the same place.</hint>
		
<fact>*Salutes Aloys* The Gallente Federation is an amalgamation of several different populations, although the Gallente are of French descent. Although even French players think the Gallente suck.</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>The Empyrean Age introduced which major game mechanic?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Factional Warfare</answer>
			
<answer>Crimewatch</answer>
			
<answer>Contracts</answer>
			
<answer>Planetary Interaction</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>It wasn't PI.</hint>
		
<fact>Empyrean Age, previously named Kali 4, is the name of the ninth expansion of Eve Online and the last one in the Kali tetralogy. It included Factional Warfare.</fact>
	
</item>
	



<item category="Lore">
		
<question>What was the first EVE expansion released?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Castor</answer>
			
<answer>Exodus</answer>
			
<answer>Bloodlines</answer>
			
<answer>Revelations I</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>It wasn't Exodus</hint>
		
<fact>Castor was the first major content addition. Release date: December 18, 2003 </fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>What year was EVE Online released?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>2003</answer>
			
<answer>2004</answer>
			
<answer>2002</answer>
			
<answer>2001</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>It was after 2001.</hint>
		
<fact>Eve Online was released in North America and Europe in May 2003.</fact>
	
</item>
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>What price is the Core Starter Pack for the game on Steam?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>£14.99</answer>
			
<answer>$14.99 </answer>
			
<answer>£12.99 </answer>
			
<answer>$19.99 </answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>14.99</hint>
		
<fact>The Core starter pack for EVE is £14.99 (Pounds). This includes various items and 30 days of game time.</fact>
	
</item>
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which expansion added the new Crimewatch system?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Retribution</answer>
			
<answer>Odyssey</answer>
			
<answer>Inferno</answer>
			
<answer>Crucible</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>It wasn't Crucible.</hint>
		
<fact>Retribution brought a revamped bounty system, a new "crimewatch" system, added 4 new destroyer ships and a new mining frigate, rebalanced the frigate, cruiser and destroyer ship roles and improved enemy AI.</fact>
	
</item>
	

</trivia>