<trivia>	

<item category="Lore">

<question> Who is the present ruler of the Amarr Empire? </question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Jamyl Sarum</answer>
			
<answer>Dochuta Karsoth</answer>
			
<answer>Excena Foer</answer>
			
<answer>Tibus Heth</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The Empress returned from death to save her people at the height of the Minmatar Rebellion </hint>
		
<fact> The Empress Jamyl Sarum rules over the Amarr Empire - http://goo.gl/Nt9i6C</fact>
	
</item>
	
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which factions have their homeworlds in the same system?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Gallente and Caldari</answer>
			
<answer>Amarr and Minmatar</answer>
			
<answer>Caldari and Amarr</answer>
			
<answer>Gallente and Minmatar</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>These two worlds are in the Luminaire System.</hint>
		
<fact>The Gallente and Caldari homeworlds are both in the Luminaire System - http://goo.gl/ngC15Y</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which company is the only Gallente company given corporation status by the Caldari State?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Quafe</answer>
			
<answer>The Scope</answer>
			
<answer>Creodron</answer>
			
<answer>Outer Ring Excavations</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>This soft drink can be found in every system in New Eden.</hint>
		
<fact>Quafe is such an important product that Quafe executives were the only people with enough vested interests on both sides to negotiate a treaty between the Gallente and Amarr - http://goo.gl/oHrirT</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which race did the Amarr fight at the battle of Vak'Atioth?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Jovian</answer>
			
<answer>Minmatar</answer>
			
<answer>Sleepers</answer>
			
<answer>Gallente</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The Amarr deeply underestimated their ancient foe at this battle.</hint>
		
<fact>The Jovian's dealt a major blow to the Amarr Empire at the Battle of Vak'Atioth - http://goo.gl/nFUeXo</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Who are referred to by the Blood Raiders as the Little Hunters?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Sisters of EVE</answer>
			
<answer>Starkmanir Tribe</answer>
			
<answer>Rogue Drones</answer>
			
<answer>Sansha's Nation</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The Blood Raiders follow the Little Hunters to disaster sights.  The Little Hunters come to help.  The Blood Raiders do not.</hint>
		
<fact>The Sisters of EVE try and make a secret of how often the Blood Raiders follow them - http://goo.gl/PX0V2m</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which race are responsible for the Rogue Drone infestation of the Galaxy?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Gallente</answer>
			
<answer>Minmatar</answer>
			
<answer>Amarr</answer>
			
<answer>Caldari</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The self aware drones are a great failure of a society that prides itself on Drone use.</hint>
		
<fact>The Gallente invented the rogue drones by accident while trying to find a replacement for human spaceship pilots - http://goo.gl/tUUilA</fact>
	
</item>
	



<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which organisation was formed to maintain the fragile piece between the five empires?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>CONCORD</answer>
			
<answer>Sisters of EVE</answer>
			
<answer>ORE</answer>
			
<answer>The Guristas</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>This organisation functions as the space police when it isn't finding compromises between the empires.</hint>
		
<fact>CONCORD was formed quickly after the empires made contact with each other to keep them from wiping each other out too soon - http://goo.gl/zF97r1</fact>
	
</item>
	


<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which race believes themselves to be the chosen ones?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Amarr</answer>
			
<answer>Caldari</answer>
			
<answer>Minmatar</answer>
			
<answer>Gallente</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The true chosen people fly through space in ships of gold.</hint>
		
<fact>The Amarr believe they are the chosen people and slavery to them is the best choice for all people - http://goo.gl/JmIW52</fact>
	
</item>
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which race was once greatest in the galaxy but have been ruined by centuries of subjugation?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Minmatar</answer>
			
<answer>Caldari</answer>
			
<answer>Amarr</answer>
			
<answer>Gallente</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>The tribes ruled their world until the golden enemy descended.</hint>
		
<fact>The Minmatar have an ancient and powerful history, before their enslavement by the Amarr - http://goo.gl/Ca959q</fact>
	
</item>
	

<item category="Lore">
		
<question>Which faction have mastered control of wormhole technology?</question>
		
<answers>
			
<answer>Sansha's Nation</answer>
			
<answer>The Amarr</answer>
			
<answer>The Serpentis</answer>
			
<answer>The Caldari</answer>
		
</answers>
		
<hint>This faction uses their mastery of wormholes in order to launch incursions into empire space.</hint>
		
<fact>Sansha's Nation have discovered how to use wormholes to strike deep into their enemies space - http://goo.gl/SUTWTg</fact>
	
</item>
	

</trivia>